USEME

Commands that can be used
"load" followed by a String representing its path then a String representing its name, with spaces in between
"save" followed by a String representing the path it will be saved to 
	then a String representing the name it will be saved as, with spaces in between
"red-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"green-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"blue-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"value-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"luma-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"intensity-component" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"horizontal-flip" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"vertical-flip" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"brighten" followed by an integer that is the brightness interval, 
	a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"darken" followed by an integer that is the darken interval, 
	a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"sepia" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"greyscale" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"blur" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between
"sharpen" followed by a String representing the name of the image to be edited 
	and a String representing the destination it will be saved to, with spaces in between

// Command that can be used for mosaic:
mosaic num-seeds source-image-name dest-image-name